ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/209
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence, Lipsig, James, Assistant Executive Secretary, 1960-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Lovestone, Jay, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Research Department, reports to GEB, 1974-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Special Assistance Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Union Health Center, 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Union Label Department, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Welfare and Health Benefits Department, 1962-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Taskforce on the Survey (Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- NY92: NY is Fashion, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Starobin, Herman, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Copies of Research Department outgoing letters, January-June, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Copies of Research Department outgoing letters, August-December, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Copies of Research Department outgoing letters, January-September, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Copies of Research Department outgoing letters, October-December, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-June, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Research Department outgoing letters, July-December, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-June, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Research Department outgoing letters, July-December, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-August, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Research Department outgoing letters, September 1971-June 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Research Department outgoing letters, July-December, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-June, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Research Department outgoing letters, July 1973-May 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Research Department outgoing letters, June-December, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-November, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Research Department outgoing letters, November 1976-December 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Research Department outgoing letters, January-December, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Research Department outgoing letters, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)